Hello friends, I hope you'll
enjoy this video. Today's topic is
slightly different from our usual topics. We
usually discuss swing trade setups,
but today it's a BTST trade setup
where we buy today and sell tomorrow, rather than
a swing trade. So, watch the video completely
until the end so that you get clarity on
what to do and what not to do. What
mistakes people usually make
in DST? If you like the video,
please like, comment, share,
subscribe, and do
n't forget to press the bell icon so that whenever we start such videos on the channel, we can get information.
Weekly Chart Analysis: This is the
weekly chart of the stock. You
can see that this stock has been
consolidating for quite some time. If you look closely, there's no
significant upward movement, no volume.
Mostly, there are doji candles
everywhere, whether it's on the upside or the downside. If you
look here, you can see that this
25 of m From here, you can see that its
shadows often reach 1240,
and if you look at the upper level, they go up to 1320.
These are one or two candles in between,
where the stock's upward movement was indicated. Again,
volume did not support it. However, you
can see that the shadows of the candles are 12, i.e.,
1320, and on the downside,
1240. If you look at it on the monthly chart as well, the
stock is consolidating.
13. But the interesting thing is that
today we are going to discuss more than a swing trade, a
BTST. Buy today, sell tomorrow,
and the reason I have brought
this setup is
because sometimes it happens that we do
not get setups in the market. Swing
trades usually do not get setups every other day.
You have to have a lot of patience for that.
Often, in this patience, there is
money in front of everyone and everyone wants to
take this trade.  And due to the
mistake of that trade, a person often loses money.
So you can say that there is a kind of
addiction in the stock market, so
often a person trades intraday. I am
not saying that most of the losses occur in intraday,
but there are more chances of incurring losses in interday.
So whenever you do
not have a swing trade setup
and you do not know what to do, then rather it is the
best thing to go for BTST where you buy
today and sell tomorrow. It is a
good setup. So I will not say that you have to
use this setup only or you should
rely a lot on this setup. See, this is a high risk
setup, but its reward is quite high, which
means the chances of loss in this are
very less. If you
watch the video completely carefully, at this time you will
understand what you have to do and what
not. So on
29th of May, you can see that this stock is
clear. I probably do
not even need to draw a line in it. This line is already
made by nature. You
can see it clearly. There is one here.
1260 is the control price, 1280
is the higher price, 30
so if we divide it equally then 20 20 20
ok now you see this
stock came at 1260 in the sec of June, next
day it opened at 1300 so you have to
keep your target here only till the control price,
that is
₹
1, you can see here also 1260, the next
day you got your 1280 1300, in this way
whenever 1260 came, the next day you got
1280, here also 1260, the next day you got 1280, here also
1260, this is a time
when you got stop loss, you can see here
1260 the next day you got your effect on the
same day, then see here also you got 1260 the next day, here also you got
1260, the next day you got
1280, then this day passed, then
this stock came for a long time  No, 1260 here
again 1260 next day you will get 1280 1260 next
day you will get 1280 1260 next day you will get 1280
1260 next day you will get 1280 1260 next day you will get 1280 again 1260 here
once stop loss was set but again the stock
rallied back up so it is
trading in a very strong range in a tight range
where you can see that the upper
trade is formed near 1320 and the
lower trade is formed near 1240 but this
is very rare 1240 and l so I would say
that if you have to keep a stop loss of 1240
if you are buying it at 1260 then you should
keep a stop loss of ₹, do not do it even at 1240 I mean
you can keep its stop loss at 1240 1230
but if you see if it has ever gone
down then it is recently  1200
or even 1220 is hardly touched and
after that there is no volume due to which
this price automatically goes back to its trading
range, so if you
can take risk then you can keep your stop loss
a little deep but if you do
not want to take risk then you can
keep your stop loss at 12:30 it is a very good setup buy
today sell tomorrow see in BTST
normally you cannot expect that I will make profit on
5, on 10, on 12, on 15 like swing
trades it is not like that, there is not much difference between swing trades
and intraday I mean sorry there is not much
difference between BTST and intraday,
intraday and BTST every person should
normally make profit on 0 to 2, I am
getting more than that, it is a very good thing
but 0 to 2% is more sufficient in BTST, in some
places you get setup of 5 also
but in this setup I believe that ₹12 on
60 you will hardly make profit maybe 2  But you will get it but
you should see how many times your stop loss was hit
in the entire time, I think once at
1221, after that once here at 1200, so if we
see and you see its winning ratio, every
time, every time, you can say
one, then you can say two, three,
four, here the stop loss was hit
five, six, seven,
eight, also see
this,
at 10, 11, the stop loss was hit at
12, you can say 12, in 12 trade setup your
stop loss was hit twice, so
10, 10 or 10 profitable trades and two losing
trades, so if you see two lost trades out of
total, sorry,
this win accuracy at 83, at 83, when your
chances of getting profit are at 83, at that time
1% more is considered, now the mistake which
most of the people make is that
they think that why don't we book profit on the same day, then it is
not necessary, now usually people will say that we should
take leverage on the same day and get high leverage  Take it and
enter the stock and the next day, I mean on the same
day we
close our trade before the market closes, so in this situation
you can see that you bought the market at 1260 and
closed at 1262 rupees.
You can see the loss here also, whenever you
think of this, if it comes to your mind that I will do
this intraday, then you can see that you will
end up in loss for a long time, loss loss or
profit, loss loss loss loss
again loss, so this setup is
not made for intraday,
if you are getting it in intraday, you
can book profit on the same day, but if you are not getting it, you will have to
hold it for the next day,
next day you will be in
profit, so this is a normal BTST
setup,
but there is risk, it is a very high risk
trait setup, but
again the win rate is quite good, I mean
out of 12 sets, your
stop loss has been hit only twice, so even those two times stop
loss, if you have risk taking capability and
you can book your  Risk, I mean you can keep your stop loss
deep below 1200
because you see, unless there are volumes,
you don't need to be afraid. Even
if the price is falling, there is a probability
that it will come back, but again, a trader's
sign is that there should be a stop loss, so I would
suggest that you consider 1230 as your stop
loss and then you have to take a position at
1260. So this is a small
educational video so that you people can
benefit from it and I am just sharing a small part of
my experience. I saw
this setup and I also
traded in it for a long time. Usually, I do
n't do it. Mostly I am in swing
trade, but
again, and I felt that it is
very important to share it with my viewers so that they can also take
advantage of all these things because usually it happens
in the market that there is nothing to do, a
lot of market choppiness is going on
and the person is sitting and gets bored, so
when there is nothing there,  You are not getting anything
and even if it is just one or two points, you are not incurring any loss. If you lose
once or twice, there will be a loss,
more than that, then there is
no loss in this setup, so this
setup is good, you can use it, okay,
I did not pay attention to the candles further, so it
can be said that you have incurred loss once more,
this is probably
1225, yes, you have incurred loss thrice, but again the
trade is quite good, the setup is
quite good, so it and if you
liked the video, please comment and share, this is
not an investment video, I am not
asking you to invest in the stock, this is a
pure educational analysis which I have
shared with you, so please please please
take any step at your own risk, till then
you guys have a great day, bye